# Violetta Thijssens

With 5+ years of experience in user-related roles in a corporate environment, I have a keen eye for the user, the product and the bottom line. I am a problem-solver, storyteller, and fast learner. I love to go the extra mile for a project and my team.

# SKILLS

## RESEARCH

- Usability Testing
- Interviews
- Online & offline Surveys
- Data Analysis
- Web Metrics
- Competitor Research
- Flow Mapping
- · Requirements Analysis

## DESIGN

- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- Sketching
- Drawing
- Copy Writing
- Visual Design

# **TECHNICAL**

- Sketch
- InVision
- Axure
- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- SQL
- Python

## COLLABORATION

- Team Player
- Communicative
- Strong Presenter
- Agile
- **Project Management**
- Facilitator
- Open to learning

## CAREER SUMMARY

#### Business Analyst H.Essers | Aug 2019-Present

#### RESPONSIBILITIES

- Requirements analysis
- User experience
- User testing

- · Set up asset management for applications
- · Delivery of upgrade project on budget
- Launch of enterprise-sized application

### Business Intelligence Engineer H.Essers | Jan 2019-Aug 2019

#### RESPONSIBILITIES

- Building user-friendly reports
- Listening to user needs
- Stakeholder management

#### ACHIEVEMENTS

- Introduction of Power BI
- · Facilitation of teamwork
- · Set up major report on transport deliveries

## Senior Data Specialist GfK | May 2018-Jan 2019

#### RESPONSIBILITIES

- · Data analysis
- Giving presentations
- Follow-up research projects

#### ACHIEVEMENTS

- · Reduction of data processing for a bimonthly report from one week to one day
- · Improved team collaboration

#### CRM Specialist Mediahuis | Oct 2016-May 2018

## RESPONSIBILITIES

- Web metrics analysis
- **Giving presentations**
- Recommendations for UX

- Ambassador for innovation
- Part of cross-departmental team to improve the customer journey

#### **Market Research Analyst** Mediahuis | Aug 2013-Oct 2016

#### RESPONSIBILITIES

- Quantitative research
- · Giving presentations

- Usability testing and interviews Set up research on digital customers
  - Research on football players that made headlines for several weeks

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Professional Diploma in UX Design**

UX DESIGN INSTITUTE & GLASGOW CALEDONIAN UNIVERISTY | COMPLETED IN 2021

#### **Writing Course**

OXFORD UNIVERSITY COMPLETED IN 2020

#### **Team Coach Course**

SYNTRA| COMPLETED IN 2020

### **Diploma in Market and Social Research Practice**

MARKET RESEARCH SOCIETY COMPLETED IN 2018

#### MA in Business, major marketing

CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY OF LEUVEN COMPLETED IN 2013 GRAPHIC DESIGNER OF STUDENT UNION